You can tell the dead by the look
in their eyes.
That woman…
was definitely dead.
No, we didn't!
I swear we didn't even touch her.
She just died on her own.
Chae-ni! Chae…
Chae-ni?
Chae-ni, where did she go?
-Mr. Son!
-She was right here.
But then,
she vanished.
What a load of nonsense. Jeju Island?
That's what I'm seeing.
Yeah, it's definitely showing Jeju.
Maybe Chae-ni's phone is glitchy.
You're the one who's glitchy.
Don't you know she hasn't once
left Haeseong since she was seven?
Yeah, I know. She's the ghost of Haeseong.
But that's what I'm seeing.
Maybe she really is in Jeju.
That silly bear isn't here either.
She packed her things?
SAVINGS ACCOUNT BANKBOOK
DEAREST GRANDMOTHER
Yes, this is Kim Jeon-bok.
I guess it really was glitchy.
It seems to have been an error.
I tried again, and she's in Haeseong.
In the Haedeul-ri area.
And the victim was Ms. Eun Chae-ni,
the granddaughter of Hearty House?
Yes.
I believe so.
Are you talking about that woman
over there?
Yes, that's right.
Isn't that Chae-ni?
THE WONDERFOOLS
EPISODE 2
SECRETS ARE MEANT TO BE KEPT
You reported the disposal
of a dead body, correct?
Deny it, okay?
Deny it, no matter what.
Deny your butt off.
-That's our only way out.
-Okay.
What dead body? Didn't you see earlier
that Eun Chae-ni is fine?
We were staking the place out
and took a tumble, okay?
Check this stink out for yourself!
I've filed countless complaints,
but the only answer I ever get is,
"No, we can't. There's nothing we can do."
You might as well just play a recording.
What else could we do?
Since the authorities wouldn't step up,
we had to catch the dumper ourselves.
What shall we do?
I guess I was mistaken.
Then we'll log this as a false alarm.
Yes. Please do that.
Okay, you can go.
We were going to. Let's go.
Hey, why would you…
What did I tell you?
I said flat-out denial would work.
You can't call it flat-out denial.
I used sound logic to persuade them.
That's the difference between me and you.
An educated person, an uneducated person.
A good person, a no-good person.
A person whose family is filthy rich,
a person who is dirt poor.
Damn it.
Hey, but are you really okay?
I totally thought you were dead.
Why weren't you breathing?
I thought I was dead too.
I even saw some weird stuff.
What ye doin' o'er there?
Don't loaf around and get outta there.
She kept saying things
that I couldn't understand.
Ain't ye hearin' me?
I said scoot on outta there!
The wind's kickin' up real bad.
At this rate, you ain't gettin' out alone.
Can't ye hear me?
I'm tellin' ya, it's mighty dicey!
What ye doin'? Get outta there already!
Maybe you had a near-death experience.
You know, not actually dying,
but just dipping your toes
into the afterlife.
Maybe you saw a grim reaper!
You think so?
So was I dead or not?
Maybe I half-died.
Like a half-dried squid or something?
Does your grandma know
the shape you're in?
Of course she doesn't.
If she did, she'd lose it.
Don't you know what she's like?
The big cheese of Myeong-dong,
King Jeon-bok.
If she finds out…
If she finds out?
EUN CHAE-NI'S
KIDNAPPERS
We're truly sorry, ma'am.
Go on and bury them.
Yes, ma'am!
Please don't do that!
Hold it!
Why are you over there, not here with us?
What was that word
I told you to memorize again?
How diplomats
get away with crimes overseas.
-Immunity.
-That's it. Granddaughter immunity.
Is there no
granddaughter's friend immunity?
What do I do now?
Hey, Mr. Son, what should we do?
Why did you rope us into this?
You could've just stolen the money.
It's okay.
We'll make sure we don't get caught.
Flat-out denial always works.
You think denial will cut it?
Is that the best you can do?
Who said you'll just deny it?
Deny with passion, with all you've got.
Would that actually work?
Then we'd be in the clear, right?
Of course. Nothing beats flat-out denial.
Did you really
think this plan through carefully?
How would you have gotten the 50 million?
Wired to my account, of course.
Borrowed accounts are illegal, you know.
I had no clue because I'd never
talked to you long enough.
That you were a girl
with such an empty head.
To think I trusted bozos like you
and co-conspired to get 50 million won…
-Want some?
-What are they?
-These are good.
-Right?
Hey, I'm talking to you!
This is my fault. It's all my fault.
I, a Homo sapiens who conspired
with Neanderthals, am to blame.
If I ever
get involved in another ridiculous
fake kidnapping of Eun Chae-ni
or another half-dried squid
near-death experience,
you can consider me…
Screwed.
She heard.
Everything.
Run!
You know the crimes you are guilty of!
Punish him mercilessly!
I am innocent. Treason, of all crimes?
This is preposterous.
I truly am innocent.
I swear to the heavens above
that I have not one speck of shame.
How dare you!
Twist his legs until he confesses!
I have done no wrong!
Is this thing really glitching?
Come out.
Come here
before I get people to drag you out!
Ms. Kim…
Could you please move…
That… No, it's okay.
Thank you.
Just moving one of your legs
is more than enough for me to get out.
Like this.
-You must be furious.
-I tried to talk her out of it.
-But it was all Chae-ni's plan.
-I said, "Think about your grandma."
-She said we'd get five million each--
-I really tried--
In other words, the three of you
staged a kidnapping for money?
-I wouldn't quite put it like that.
-Mr. Son here wouldn't fix my roof.
-Chae-ni planned all of this--
-I just wanted my roof--
Where's your mastermind, Eunie?
That's exactly it!
Eun Chae-ni is the mastermind, Ms. Kim.
Eunie.
Your accomplices have already betrayed you
without hesitation. Get out here.
Why, you always make
things worse for yourself!
Get out here!
What?
I definitely saw her climb in here.
Where were you hiding?
Grandma.
Can you see me?
What newfangled nonsense is this?
Did you think I wouldn't be able
to see you? Get out now!
Deary me.
What do I do, Grandma?
Something must be really wrong with me.
I keep seeing things. What do I do?
How?
What feels wrong? How?
Should I call the hospital director?
-I don't know.
-Are you running a fever?
-Oh dear.
-I just…
Would you look at that?
She's using her granddaughter immunity.
Tell me what happened.
-Just now, I was in some weird…
-Yes, what is it?
-Yes?
-Grandma!
Breathe. Just breathe. And sit down.
Sit right here and take a deep breath.
Just take a breath.
He's annoying.
He's annoying? That's no good.
Hey, you're annoying her!
You're looking for someone?
Who?
The Child of Eternity?
I don't know.
There were some children
who survived the fire back then.
But I'm not sure about
this Child of Eternity you speak of.
Oh, but I do remember
one other child very clearly.
Number 3972.
Because I saved him
from the fire that day.
Sir!
Please open this door!
Number 3972?
You saved that child?
Yes, I sure did.
And that child
has returned to Haeseong.
He's grown into a fine young man.
He didn't seem to recognize me,
but I recognized him right away.
Number 3972.
I'm certain it's him.
I see.
Thank you for telling me.
Here, eat up before it gets cold.
I don't know how many years it's been
since I sat across from you like this…
and ate a hot meal.
After you died,
I was sure a day like this
would never come again.
I'm so glad you're here.
Did you hear that? Number 3972.
Honey.
Honey!
Where… where am I?
Honey?
NUMBER 3972
ABILITY: TELEKINESIS
What is all this?
Don't you have a family?
I don't know.
I can't remember.
Not even your mom's face?
Or your dad's?
Don't worry.
I can't die.
You can't die?
Focus and try again. You can do it.
How did he do that?
That's awesome.
Stop!
You're still doing this, City Hall guy?
I asked you
to please keep it down at night!
You're really trying my patience.
Knock it off or move out already!
I can't die.
But that kid was definitely
a boy.
What…
Huh?
How?
Why, what is it?
Is something wrong? Is it very serious?
Well, it's…
I'm ready for anything, so just tell me.
Spit it out!
Well,
it's very…
I don't quite understand
how this has happened either,
but the test results are…
Everything here
looks normal.
Come again?
If you look at the graphs here,
you can see they're all very stable
with no major fluctuations.
This is from last time. This is now.
I checked the ultrasound results, too,
and her kidneys look clean.
Even the valvular inflammation
I saw last time is completely gone.
And this is the X-ray we just took.
That one's from last time.
Her lungs have cleared up too.
Last time, her heart was this big,
but now,
it's back to a completely normal size.
So, you're saying…
To get this straight,
you seem to be saying
that everything has improved.
Would that be right?
No, ma'am, it's not just an improvement.
She's in
perfect health.
How?
Exactly! I've never seen
anything like this before.
Of course, once in a blue moon,
things like this do happen,
and there's no telling why.
We usually call them miracles.
I think, ma'am, that Chae-ni
has been blessed with a miracle.
A miracle?
This child is a miracle child.
CHOI YEONG-JUN
This is Choi Yeong-jun.
Please leave a message.
Hello, Director Choi. It's me.
King Jeon-bok of Myeong-dong.
Call me when you get this.
CHURCH OF ETERNAL SALVATION
APOCALYPSE ON DECEMBER 31ST
RECEIVE SALVATION
AND BE GRANTED ETERNAL LIFE
APOCALYPSE
SALVATION
What do we do now, Mr. Son?
How will we ever face Ms. Kim now?
You tell me.
I refused, but you two insisted on
roping me into this. So tell me.
Mr. Son.
If you hadn't assumed Chae-ni was dead,
we wouldn't be in this mess.
Assumed?
Listen.
She was definitely dead.
She didn't have a pulse.
How could a dead person come back to life?
You went as far as to dispose of
a perfectly healthy person in the hills.
Quiet. Temporarily laid to rest,
not disposed of.
Besides, did I act alone?
You're even worse than I am.
How could you, her friend,
dump her body in a garbage pit?
Mr. Son!
That's why I said we shouldn't do it.
Of course, there it is!
There go the waterworks again.
You look like a thug,
but you cry and sulk at the drop of a hat!
Do you know how ghastly
your crying face is?
Don't make fun of people's looks.
You shouldn't do that.
Do you think I'm making fun of your looks?
I'm not.
Wait, you weren't? Really?
Of course not.
I was going for a double whammy
by making fun of your looks and sulkiness.
Get a clue, Sappy Sap.
With your runny nose.
God, you drive me nuts.
I told you not to drink from the bottle.
By the way,
any news about the illegal dumping
in the hills?
What?
Right, that.
I actually went earlier
and gave them a good talking-to.
Any time now. Don't worry.
And your mother?
What?
Did you make it clear to her
that we're not sending her to Hawaii
but the Hawaii Resort in Bugok?
Yeah, that. Well, you know…
She knows our situation, after all.
She didn't seem too disappointed.
What are you even doing?
I just have some things to think about.
Do you have to do it there?
Yeah, I have to do it here.
Well, I'm going to bed.
Okay, good night, Ms. Moon Mi-hui.
Here comes my daughter, Cheong,
just as I was opening the fridge door.
Want some ice to cool down?
So that's a no?
Are you the problem or am I?
If you are, I can call for a repair,
but who do I call if I'm the problem?
How can this…
How…
Who exactly were your accomplices?
I acted alone.
Ro-bin and Sonie from the flower shop.
I know those two idiots were involved.
Was there anyone else?
I told you. The three of us acted alone.
Do you not know what "alone" means?
I sure do. I know very well.
The soup's getting cold. Eat.
How did you even plan to travel
without a passport?
What did the doctor say?
Did he give you some bad news?
While you were growing up,
there wasn't a day that I didn't pray
nor a single day I had peace of mind.
If I couldn't reach you for just a moment,
my heart would sink.
Every time I took you to the hospital,
my blood ran cold.
That's how scared I've been
for the past 20 years.
But
no matter how scared I was…
I doubt I was as scared as you.
I'm sorry, Grandma.
What are you sorry for?
You've made me
the happiest I've been in 27 years.
The test results were excellent.
He said everything's normal.
I never thought I'd see this day.
You're as clean as a whistle.
The size, shape, and condition
of your heart are all perfect.
Why, that doctor
made a huge fuss, calling it a miracle.
So,
from now on,
live your life to the fullest, okay?
But don't let your guard down
and get regular checkups.
What was it, again?
Go see the northern lights or whatever
and that huge-headed rock.
And what was it?
Go see the Iguana Falls or whatever.
And go explore Africa.
You should do it all.
So,
from now on,
live life to the fullest, okay?
Make the darn most of it,
and pay for your own trips.
How will I ever earn enough
peeling onions?
Grandma!
Before that…
REWARD GRAPES
…you need to fill this up.
Until then,
be good, stay healthy, and speak politely.
And don't spit on other people's houses.
Then I'll give these to you.
Come on, Grandma. I'm not seven.
I'm 27 years old.
If you don't like it, best get peeling.
Oh no.
All right.
First, eat all your food.
Yes, this is Kim Jeon-bok of Hearty House.
It's been a while, Director Choi.
"Great job."
No more purple lips.
No more dull skin.
No more tinnitus.
And no more bruises.
Even my heart's beating fine.
There's been a definite improvement
since my near-death experience.
So why do I keep seeing things?
What ye doin'? Get outta there already!
But that place
wasn't even a tunnel.
Could it be time…
I can't even bring myself
to say "time travel."
That's right.
My brain must have been
deprived of oxygen for a long time.
That's for certain.
There's no doubt they were hallucinations.
Wait a minute.
Then in exchange for a working heart…
7 times 5 is 35, 7 times 6 is 42,
7 times 7 is 49…
-7 times 8 is…
-Don't touch your eyes, idiot!
Did I lose my brain
in exchange for a working heart?
-This can't be.
-Chae-ni, you have a guest outside.
It's a guy.
He's a looker.
Don't touch your eyes. It stings.
Don't move.
Why are you here?
What do you want from me?
Here to pay up?
How many times have you died?
Me?
Was that the first time?
Or have you died before?
Is he saying he wants to die?
No. That's him.
The guy who reported us
for dumping a body.
When you had
that near-death experience yesterday.
I see.
First, you wreck my suitcase,
then you make a big fuss over nothing?
I reported it for your sake.
So they could at least find your body.
My body?
I'm standing right here, alive and well!
-You were definitely dead.
-No, I wasn't!
You're making me sound like
some kind of freak.
So what happened?
It's a secret.
She's definitely hiding something.
So you can't tell me?
It's a secret because I can't tell you.
It wouldn't be a secret
if I could tell you, would it?
Then, have you ever…
heard of Wunderkinder?
What's this
Boon… the King Duck?
I don't even like duck.
Is it a new duck joint or something?
Why do you keep bothering us?
We told you that nothing happened.
See? Nothing happened.
Well, okay, then.
If you say so.
What was that?
We've got ourselves a nutjob, right?
What if he finds out about the kidnapping?
It was my idea anyway.
But Mr. Son said we could be in trouble
if the police find out!
They'd have no evidence anyway.
You grabbed my suitcase
and camcorder, didn't you?
No. They're probably still
in the abandoned greenhouse.
You didn't delete the footage?
No.
You died,
and we were so freaked out that--
Oh, for God's sake!
You're peeling my share
of the onions for today.
And tomorrow and the day after that
and after that! All yours!
Mr. Son? It's Ro-bin.
Okay, goober. Talk later.
I knew I shouldn't have gotten mixed up
with those bozos.
Everything's going sideways.
Please, Rala.
Why are you giving me a hard time too?
That's it, you beauty.
Okay, your turn for lunch.
Today's menu is jjajangbap. Go eat.
Un-jeong, you should also…
You're already gone.
He went alone again, that brat.
Oh boy.
There's only one way to find out for sure
if she possesses
the ability to resurrect.
Make her need to revive herself.
Extra crispy.
But what if
I'm wrong?
Excuse me.
HAEWON FLOWERS
Is it broken or something?
Why isn't it working?
It'll be worth more if it's working.
What the…
Chae-ni. Chae-ni?
What's wrong with her?
Delete that.
-What's this?
-What? Why?
What is it?
What's wrong with Chae-ni?
And what's wrong with you?
Chae-ni
is dead.
I'll buy this from you.
Where the heck did they leave them?
Did they really leave them here?
This is it?
Where's the other stuff?
Damn it.
That bumbling idiot.
How could he leave that stuff there?
What's going on? What's happening?
Where are you right now?
What?
Where else would I be?
I'm making a delivery, of course.
Well, if the flowers
you're supposed to deliver are right here,
what exactly are you delivering?
What?
What the…
What do you mean, what?
I should be asking you!
What exactly are you doing?
-What…
-What?
-What?!
Honey, I gotta go.
Did he just
hang up on me?
What's happening?
I need to get out! Let me out!
What is this?
No way, right?
Lady Trainwreck isn't…
She isn't in there right now, is she?
-That fool still dares to lie!
-Could we get more bracken?
-Coming right up.
-You there!
Twist the legs of the traitor who…
-You scared me!
-That table wants more bracken.
Can't you take it to them?
It's the final scene.
Yes, just a moment.
-Hey, they slipped up!
-Where?
You missed it.
Go on and behead me!
LOCATION PROVIDED BY KOREAN FOLK VILLAGE
-Hey, look right there!
-Where?
Oh, I see it!
I heard they shoot scenes live nowadays.
Looks like it's true.
A hospital gown in the Joseon Dynasty?
Why, that's something.
I bet someone's in big trouble.
I'm the one who caught it.
Oh, right.
Hello.
Honey.
Yes, sure. I'm heading back right now.
No, I had some business
to quickly attend to at City Hall.
No, right now, I'm…
I'm already on my way back.
What?
No, I swear. I'll be back soon.
Why's this happening again?
Stop trying to change the subject.
When will you be back?
What?
I…
An hour?
The thing is,
I'm going as fast as I can,
but there's traffic--
Fine, I was playing hooky. So what?
You think all I have to do
is make deliveries?
I have personal business too.
Okay?
The person I hate most in the world
might be in danger.
So hang up, and don't wait for me.
I'm busy!
What is that?
Number 3972.
So you're looking for something too.
Her power isn't resurrection?
Could it be…
Wow, this is insane.
Now she's in international waters?
It was teleportation?
When did you board?
Are you a police officer?
What did that bitch see
to have such a dumb look on her face?
Stop yapping.
Let's not waste time
and just throw her overboard as fish food!
Okay.
Help me.
Has Madam King arrived already?
Long time no see, Director Choi.
LIFETIME ACHIEVEMENT AWARD
CHOI YEONG-JUN
Subtitle translation by: Jimin Choi